<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Dai</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Dai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Michael&#39;s Hospital ED Nurse Assignment App</title>
      <link>/projects/2019-06-15-rn-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/2019-06-15-rn-assignment/</guid>
      <description>This post was originally posted here.
Intro The St. Michael’s Hospital (SMH) Emergency Department (ED) is divided into clinical areas; each area has a requisite number of nurses. Each shift, nurses are assigned to work in a specific clinical area or a leadership role. This is known as the nurse assignment task. Optimal nurse assignment is essential for ensuring optimal patient care and improving staff satisfaction.
 The Problem Nurse assignment is a daily task at the SMH ED.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>--  -- -- -- Hi! I&#39;m David Dai.  --  
I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Scientist. I take data and extract information that can be used to reduce inefficiencies and improve outcomes.
I am trained in applied statistics and machine learning.
I have extensive experience in the healthcare sector, but am interested in a multitude of areas, including technology, education, and hockey analytics.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not working, I enjoy fitness and watching the Toronto Maple Leafs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to chat about statistics, data science, machine learning, or something I&amp;rsquo;ve written about, send me a message!
You can also find me on Linkedin and Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>